

## CONTACTS

+38 (067) 9405945 paseka09@ukr.com <u>LinkedIn</u>

**Telegram** 

Khmelnytskyi Region, Ukraine

## TECH SKILLS

TestReil

• HTML

• jira

• CSS

Postman

JSON

Dbeaver

XML

DevTools

SQL

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Collaboration
- Adaptability
- Persistence
- Critical thinking
- Ability to listen and ask questions

### LANGUAGES

- English (Pre -Intermediate)
- Polish (Elementary)
- Ukraine (Native)

## **EDUCATION**

Nov 2023 - March 2024IT School GoIT

• QA Engineer

2004 - 2005

Kamianets-Podilskyi National University nomine Ivan Ogienko

Master of Psychology

1992 - 1997

Khmelnytskyi National University

• Master of Economics

# Liudmyla Pasieka

## Junior QA engineer

## Summary

I am a motivated and goal-oriented Junior QA Engineer with a technical foundation and a strong desire to grow in Software testing. I have good experience in manual testing, creating test cases, checklists, and bug reports. I have finished a course about QA engineering recently. I am still studying new tools for being the best QA specialist.

My goal is to get a job in a reputed company where I will be able to achieve success. I am sure that my new skills and knowledge as well as my great previous work experience, especially my extremely huge desire to develop as a specialist in the field of Quality Assurance will greatly benefit the company.

## **Pet-Projects**

- <u>Eldorado</u> manual testing of functionality at the acceptance level; creating a checklist and bug reports
- Slack creating a checklist for performing smoke testing
- Trello -testing of API by Postman
- <u>GoIT website</u> Studying Website Requirement Specification documents; creating test cases according to Website Requirement Specification; bug reports based on executed test cases
- <u>MakeUp</u> -working with DevTools, analysis of requests, their methods, and statuses
- <u>SQL requests</u> -creation of SQL queries using the educational database with Dbeaver

## **Work Experience**

• Employment Service

Sep. 2014-Present

#### A head of the department in Letychiv

- manage the process of providing quality services to customers
- organize meetings with employers and partners to agree on ways of cooperation
- lead, mentor, and manage a high-performing social team, fostering a collaborative and results-driven work environment
- provide quality and effective services to customers
- developed a set of filters for analyzing the proper functioning of the internal program. This enables quick and high-quality control over compliance with the technology of service provision and the accuracy of payments

## Employment Service

Jan. 2008-Aug. 2014

#### A deputy head of the department in Letychiv

- carried out an analysis of the qualitative and quantitative characteristics of the markers of achieving results
- monitored and controlled compliance with the technology of providing services to customers
- advised customers of the employment service on the application of employment legislation
- · organized and conducted specialist training
- Employment Service

Sep. 2005-Dec. 2007

#### Specialist of the department in Letychiv

- carried out individual reception of customers
- provided job selection services to clients of the service
- organized and conducted group meetings and trainings
- advised customers of the employment service